A Fairly Odd Christmas is a family, fantasy, tv movie
film directed by Savage Steve Holland.
After Timmy Turner causes Santa amnesia he must become
the new Santa in order to save Christmas.
Timmy Turner, played by Drake Bell.
Tootie, played by Daniella Monet.
Denzel Crocker, played by David James Lewis.
Cosmo (voice) / Mr. Turner, played by Daran Norris.
Mrs. Turner, played by Teryl Rothery.
Christmas Carol, played by Devyn Dalton.
A Fairly Odd Christmas (also known as A Fairly Odd Movie 2) is a 2012
American live-action/animated Christmas comedy television film.
It is the sequel to the 2011 live-action TV film A
Fairly Odd Movie: Grow Up, Timmy Turner!
and the second live-action adaptation of the Nickelodeon
animated television series The Fairly OddParents.
The film was first announced on March 14, 2012.
The film premiered on Nickelodeon on November 29,
2012, to 4.473 million viewers.
The film was released on Region 1 DVD on December 17, 2013, and
was released on Blu-ray on December 4, 2015.
The film explores themes of holiday, christmas, live action and animation.